

Quentin ANDRÈS

Bachelor in Health and Life sciences, major in molecular biology and genetics. Currently applying for a Master of Science program.

Rigorous and endowed with a good team spirit, I am motivated to acquire new knowledge and develop my skills as part of a future training in molecular biology and genetics. I would also like, during my studies, to gain international experience during an internship or a semester abroad if this is possible.

CONTACTS



+33 (0) 6 79 14 62 78



quentin.ls.andres@gmail.com



305 Chemin des moyennes breguières, Antibes



21 ans



Linked in. https://www.linkedin.com/in/ quentinandres/

SKILLS

Laboratory techniques

- Cell culture techniques
- Purification and separation of nucleic acid sequences
- Technical expertise of qPCR and qRT-**PCR**
- Molecular biology techniques: cloning, recombination and mutagenesis, transfection and cell transformation

Computer skills

Programming: R, Python

Pack Office: Word, Excel, Powerpoint

Linguistics

French native	
English	
Spanish	
Slovak	\bullet
Chinese	

EDUCATION

2016-2019

Bachelor of Science in Life Science and Health University of Nice Côte d'Azur – faculty of sciences

2019 – 2020 Bsc year 3 - Major Molecular Biology and Genetics **2018 – 2019 Bsc year 2** - Major Molecular Biology and Genetics

2016 - 2018 Bsc year 1 - Life Science and Health

2014-2016

Lycée Jacques Audiberti - Antibes French Baccalauréat - Major in Life Science - Major in Life Science and Physics.

EXPERIENCE

2019-2020

Providing french language courses to foreigners on internet

2007-2014

Antibes School of Music Jazz drums class and music theory class

2012-2013

Internship at Métropole de Nice Côte d'Azur, Departement of Geographic Information

- Hands-on Geographic information system (GIS)
- Discovery of SIG ArcMap software
- Observation of tramway deployment project

HOBBIES

Practice of drums Music Travel Slovakia, Hungary, Czech Republic, USA, Spain, Turkey, Italy, Réunion island Alpin ski, fitness/body-building Sport